Guide to the H.E Butti Bin Bishr Collection AD.MC.093
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Hunting and Fishing Trips in the UAE and Abroad
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Sultan Bin Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.H. Sheikh Mubarak Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr on a hunting trip., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref23_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 10.1 x 15.2 cm (E-records AD_MC
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Hunting; Presidents; Royalty; Pakistan; Facial Hair; Officials; Boys; Children; Clocks/Watches; Guns; Weapons; Birds; Animals; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Gatherings; Arabic Writing; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - A group of people preparing meat on a hunting trip, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle)., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref23_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 14.2 x 18.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Deserts; Hunting; Men; Group Portraits; Girls; Children; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Tents; Carpets/Rugs; Regional/National Dress; Officials
  - A group of men sitting on the Corniche in Abu Dhabi, including H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (right), H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan (second from the right), H.H. Sheikh Saif Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan (middle, face showing), and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left)., 1967; AD_MC_093_ref23_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 14.2 x 18.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Streets/Roads; Beaches; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the left: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, an unidentified man, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Ma'ouf Mohammed Al Amri, H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba, and H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi on a fishing boat., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref23_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 20.5 x 25.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Officials; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Presidents; Royalty; Fishing; Water; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the left: an unidentified man, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, Ma'ouf Mohammed Al Amri, H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba, and H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi on a fishing boat., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref23_000011_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 20.5 x 25.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Water; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Facial Hair; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the left: an unidentified man, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, an unidentified man, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Ma'ouf Mohammed Al Amri, and H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba on a fishing boat., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref23_000012_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 20.5 x 25.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Water; Boats/Ships; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Transportation; Regional/National Dress; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Fishing; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Hats; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on a hunting trip in the north of Scotland, with H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba on the right., 20 August 1968; AD_MC_093_ref23_000013_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Presidents; Hunting; Royalty; Facial Hair; Scotland, UK; Birds; Hats; Officials; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Images of Official and Casual Events
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr smoking in his office in Abu Dhabi., Circa 1973; AD_MC_093_ref24_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 17.2 x 12.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Offices; Books; Telephones; Officials; Furnishings
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr walking on a street in Syria., Circa 1974-1975; AD_MC_093_ref24_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.8 x 13.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Officials; Syria; Streets/Roads
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) standing in an airplane upon arriving to a country., Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref24_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Men; Group Portraits; Airplanes; Transportation; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Microphones; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Unknown Locations; Officials; Facial Hair
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr smoking on a boat., Circa 1970-1972; AD_MC_093_ref24_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 14 x 18.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Water; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Cigarettes; Smoking; Officials; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1972-1973; AD_MC_093_ref24_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 9.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Clocks/Watches; Facial Hair; Individual Portraits; Unknown Locations
  - A group portrait of five men in suits, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle, front) and Dawood Al Siksik (right, front)., Circa 1966-1967; AD_MC_093_ref24_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.4 x 14.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Officials; Drinks/Beverages; Furnishings; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Unknown Locations
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) with Mohammed Bin Ahmad Bin Dasmal sitting in armchairs., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref24_000007_000001; Eveready Studio, (Karachi, Pakistan); 1 Photographic Prints 16.3 x 11.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates; Furnishings; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) talking with two unidentified people., Circa 1972-1973; AD_MC_093_ref24_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 19.9 x 15 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Women; United Arab Emirates; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr sitting wearing a fur hat and holding a cane., Circa 1973-1975; AD_MC_093_ref24_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Hats; Canes/Walking Sticks; Men; Individual Portraits; Carpets/Rugs; Furnishings; Officials; Unknown Locations; Facial Hair
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr wearing a suit in a garden in Morocco., Circa 1973-1975; AD_MC_093_ref24_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Facial Hair; Buildings; Architecture; Gardens; Officials; Morocco; Fountains
  - Members of the Emirati delegation swimming in a pool on a trip overseas, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right, in pool)., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref24_000011_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Swimming; Swimming Pools; Men; Group Portraits; Umbrellas/Parasols; Unknown Locations; Women; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr standing under a chandelier., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref24_000012_000001; Badr, Mohammed (United Arab Emirates); 1 Photographic Prints 12.6 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Men; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Officials; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Chandeliers; Furnishings; Mirrors; Carpets/Rugs; Facial Hair; Unknown Locations
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr playing pool in Spain., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref24_000013_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.6 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Restaurants/bars; Men; Individual Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials; Spain; Arabic Writing
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr in the swimming pool at the Khawaneej Palace., Circa 1974; AD_MC_093_ref24_000014_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.6 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Swimming; Swimming Pools; Men; Individual Portraits; Palaces; Umbrellas/Parasols; Palm Trees; Water; Officials; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) with two unidentified men on an airplane., Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref24_000015_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 19 x 14.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Airplanes; Transportation; Officials; Unknown Locations; Clocks/Watches
  - A group portrait of five men in suits, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle, front) and Dawood Al Siksik (right, front)., Circa 1966-1967; AD_MC_093_ref24_000016_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.4 x 14.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Drinks/Beverages; Furnishings; Officials; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Unknown Locations
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) holding a pipe next to an unidentified man., Circa 1973-1974; AD_MC_093_ref24_000017_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.8 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Carpets/Rugs; Unknown Locations; Officials; Tobacco pipes; Clocks/Watches
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr wearing sunglasses., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref24_000018_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 19 x 14.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Officials; United Arab Emirates
  - A portrait of H.E Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1967-1968; AD_MC_093_ref24_000019_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 21 x 14.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Unknown Locations; Clocks/Watches
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr sleeping in an armchair., Circa 1967-1968; AD_MC_093_ref24_000020_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 14 x 19.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Furnishings; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials; Unknown Locations; Clocks/Watches; Books
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) practicing for an interview in his office in Abu Dhabi., Circa 1970-1972; AD_MC_093_ref24_000021_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.8 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Furnishings; Offices; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Men; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Officials; Bags/Purses; Facial Hair
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr talking with three members of a foreign delegation., Circa 1970; AD_MC_093_ref24_000022_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.2 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cigarettes; Smoking; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Unknown Locations; Gatherings
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr in the swimming pool at the Khawaneej Palace., Circa 1974; AD_MC_093_ref24_000023_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.2 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Water; Swimming; Swimming Pools; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Facial Hair; Officials
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr holding a telephone in his office., Circa 1970-1972; AD_MC_093_ref24_000024_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 14.1 x 19 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Offices; Furnishings; Men; Telephones; Officials; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr holding a telephone in his office., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref24_000025_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Telephones; Individual Portraits; Men; Offices; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Officials
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr on a trip to Scotland., Circa 1967-1968; AD_MC_093_ref24_000026_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.1 x 20.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Scotland, UK; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Hunting; Men; Officials
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr drinking tea., Circa 1972; AD_MC_093_ref24_000027_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24.2 x 17.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Furnishings; Tea/Coffee; Drinks/Beverages; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Clocks/Watches; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Carpets/Rugs; Officials
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr in an office., Circa 1973; AD_MC_093_ref24_000028_000001; Harrison Gore Films, 10 Stratford Place, London (England, UK); 1 Photographic Prints 20.3 x 25.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Furnishings; Facial Hair; London, England, UK; Offices; Officials
- Studio Portraits of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr driving a truck with two unidentified men, one stands in front of a truck., Circa 1964; AD_MC_093_ref25_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 14 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Streets/Roads; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr at his desk in his office in Abu Dhabi., January 1975; AD_MC_093_ref25_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.9 x 12.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Men; Individual Portraits; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Telephones; Offices; Furnishings; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) with an unidentified man in Ad-Dammān, Saudi Arabia., Circa 1963-1964; AD_MC_093_ref25_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 13.5 x 8.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Studio Photography; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Painted Backdrops; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Ad-Dammān, Saudi Arabia
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr holding a bottle of Old Spice at his desk in his office in Abu Dhabi., Circa 1971-1972; AD_MC_093_ref25_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Men; Individual Portraits; Offices; Officials; Furnishings; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Clocks/Watches
  - An envelope with Arabic handwriting that says, "To Butti Bin Bishr.", Circa 1971-1972; AD_MC_093_ref25_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 15.2 x 10.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Arabic Writing; Unknown Locations
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref25_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.6 x 4.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Men; United Arab Emirates; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Studio Photography; Officials
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1970-1975; AD_MC_093_ref25_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 5.8 x 4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates; Studio Photography; Officials
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1960-1962; AD_MC_093_ref25_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.3 x 6 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Officials; Studio Photography; United Arab Emirates
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1970-1972; AD_MC_093_ref25_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 5 x 3.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials; United Arab Emirates
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1970-1972; AD_MC_093_ref25_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 5.8 x 4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; United Arab Emirates; Officials
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1955-1959; AD_MC_093_ref25_000011_000001; Orient Studio, (United Arab Emirates); 1 Photographic Prints 8.8 x 6.6 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Officials; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1970-1972; AD_MC_093_ref25_000012_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 7.4 x 5.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Studio Photography; United Arab Emirates; Officials
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1955-1959; AD_MC_093_ref25_000013_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6 x 4.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Studio Photography; Regional/National Dress; Officials; United Arab Emirates
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1970-1972; AD_MC_093_ref25_000014_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.7 x 4.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Individual Portraits; Men; Studio Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1980-1985; AD_MC_093_ref25_000015_000001; Schulze, Frank; 1 Photographic Prints 6.3 x 5.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Men; Color Photography; United Arab Emirates; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Studio Photography; Officials
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1975-1979; AD_MC_093_ref25_000016_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.5 x 6 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; United Arab Emirates
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1970-1972; AD_MC_093_ref25_000017_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 7.3 x 5.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair; Men; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Officials; United Arab Emirates
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., 8 February 1972; AD_MC_093_ref25_000018_000001; Studio Jammal (United Arab Emirates); 1 Photographic Prints 6.4 x 4.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Studio Photography; United Arab Emirates
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., 1969; AD_MC_093_ref25_000019_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.6 x 4.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Facial Hair; Officials; United Arab Emirates
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1955-1959; AD_MC_093_ref25_000020_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.1 x 8.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Officials; Facial Hair; Studio Photography; United Arab Emirates
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., 7 February 1972; AD_MC_093_ref25_000021_000001; Studio Jammal (United Arab Emirates); 1 Photographic Prints (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Men; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates
- H.E. Butti Bin Bishr's Visit to UAE-Sponsored Students in Cairo
  - A group of men and children sitting in arm chairs, including Khalid Bin Mohammed Bin Sulaiman (left), H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the right), and Rashid Bin Bishr (child)., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref26_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 7.1 x 9.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Boys; Children; Students; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Cairo, Egypt; Officials
  - A group of men and children sitting in arm chairs, including Khalid Bin Mohammed Bin Sulaiman (left), an unidentified man, Abdullah Belhoul, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right), and Rashid Bin Bishr (child)., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref26_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 7.1 x 9.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Boys; Children; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Cairo, Egypt; Students; Officials; Telephones; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) with an unidentified man in a field., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref26_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.7 x 13.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Forest/Woodlands; Cairo, Egypt; Group Portraits; Officials; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr in front of the Great Pyramids., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref26_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 13.8 x 8.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Giza, Egypt; Officials; Pyramids; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - A group of students sitting on a curb with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (third from right), Rashid Bin Bishr (second from the right), Abdullah Belhoul (second from the left), and Ali Al Budoor (far right)., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref26_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.7 x 13.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Children; Boys; Group Portraits; Students; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Cairo, Egypt; Streets/Roads; Officials
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr on a sailboat on the Nile River., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref26_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.7 x 13.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)